visiondirect.com 2015-03-15

# Vision Direct - Contact Lenses: Order Discount Contact Lenses Acuvue, Acuvue 2, Focus, Freshlook Online

|  |  | 

**TRUSTe Licensee**

drugstore.com, inc. wants you to feel secure when visiting [www.VisionDirect.com](http://www.visiondirect.com/?atrx=dps-16&atrxp1=148603&atrxp2=1&atrxp3=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2EVisionDirect%2Ecom&atrxp4=148605) and is committed to maintaining your privacy when you do so. This privacy policy explains our policies and practices regarding the collection, use, storage, and disclosure of your personal information by Vision Direct Inc., a subsidiary of drugstore.com, inc. (“Vision Direct”, “we”, “us”).

We have been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and our practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. This statement discloses the privacy practices for Vision Direct. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@visiondirect.com](mailto:privacy@visiondirect.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). 

**Information We Collect**   
We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect on our websites to provide you with a superior shopping experience and to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions. 

**Your Account**   
When you place an order, we will ask you to set up "my account," which includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date, as well as certain other information when you order prescriptions. Using your account information, we will send you communications that we believe are relevant to you, including eMedalert™ recall notices, prescription refill and renewal reminders, newsletters, and e-mails. If you prefer not to receive optional e-mails or other communications from us, you may adjust your account to prevent such communications by clicking on "subscriptions" within "my account," by contacting us at [unsubscribe@visiondirect.com](mailto:unsubscribe@visiondirect.com), or by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link included in any of our e-mail messages. 

If you would like to review or revise the information we have in your account, you may access such information by clicking on the "my account" link below or on any screen of our site. 

**Customer Reviews**   
We are pleased to hear from our customers and welcome your comments regarding our products. We include customer reviews on our website to allow other customers to see what you think about a product. These reviews may contain personally identifiable information, such as your name, should you choose to use your first and/or last name. We also allow you the option of sharing your review anonymously by entering a “nickname” when submitting your review. To request removal of your personal information from these reviews, contact us at [privacy@visiondirect.com](mailto:privacy@visiondirect.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Your Health Information**   
To fill your prescription contact lens order, we collect the following additional information: your date of birth, prescription information, and doctor or clinic information (including name, address, and phone number of your prescriber). 

**Information Automatically Collected**  
We automatically receive and collect certain types of information whenever you visit our websites. For example, like many other websites, we use "cookies" and web beacons (described below) and obtain certain types of information when your browser accesses our websites. This information includes the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, your geographic location as determined by your IP address, your browser software and operating system, your web server, the date and time you access our site, session information (such as download errors and page response times), information about your viewing, search and purchase history, and information about the referring URL and the URL clickstream to, through, and from our websites. We use this information to monitor the usage and performance of our site, to enhance our customers' search and shopping experiences and to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. Some web browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” feature that signals to websites that you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Please note that visiondirect.com does not interpret or respond to “Do Not Track” signals. 

If you would like more information about these practices or to learn about your options for not having this information used, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Information From Third Parties**   
If we receive updated account information from third parties, we may revise your account for you so that we can efficiently process your orders, deliver your packages, or otherwise communicate with you. For example, we may receive customer information from our shippers or from third parties with which we operate co-branded businesses. In addition, we may acquire customer names, e-mail addresses, and mailing addresses for select mailings from third parties. 

**Other Information You Provide**   
We collect additional information that you choose to give us. For example, you provide information to us when you complete surveys or sweepstakes/contest entry forms, add items to Your List™, sign up for special discounts or coupons, communicate with us by e-mail, phone or otherwise, provide product reviews, or provide alternative delivery addresses.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**

We protect all of your information against unauthorized access or release. We share your personal and prescription information with third parties as follows: 

  * Flexible Spending Account (FSA) Purchases – When you make a purchase from Vision Direct of FSA-reimbursable items that will be automatically deducted from your FSA account (i.e., if you use your FSA-approved credit or debit card to make the purchase or if we have an arrangement with your FSA administrator to provide electronic substantiation on your behalf), we share with your FSA administrator a list of the FSA-eligible products you purchased, together with such account, transaction, and payment information as may be requested by your FSA administrator for the purpose of substantiating and tracking your purchase. We do not share with your FSA administrator information about non-FSA items you purchase. 

  * Brand Manufacturers - We may develop programs with some of our brand manufacturers through which you may be offered special discounts or coupons on products in exchange for providing your e-mail address or completing a survey about the manufacturer's products. When you are offered such discounts or coupons in exchange for providing information (for example, giving your e-mail address or completing a survey), you will be notified that if you choose to participate, your name, e-mail address, and responses will be shared with the brand manufacturer. We will share no other information. 

  * Business Transfers - We may buy or sell stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information is usually treated as one of the transferred business assets. Should Vision Direct Inc., or substantially all of its assets be sold, customer information will be one of the transferred business assets. In that event, we will post a notification on this page or send you an e-mail so that you are always aware of how we are using your information. 

  * Compliance with Law; Protection of Rights, Property, or Safety - We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, and/or legal process served on us; and/or to protect our rights and the rights of our customers; or to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or other policies or user agreements. 

  * As You Direct - If you direct us to, we will release other personally identifiable information to your authorized representative, specified marketing partners, or such other person as you may direct. At the direction of the customer and to the extent specifically authorized by law, we will release such information to other persons, including specified marketing partners. 

  * From time to time, we may partner with certain companies who, in conjunction with membership programs, subscription services, or rewards programs, require that we disclose purchase or other personal information about their members who visit our website (for example, to earn points for purchases made on our site through links from the partner site). We will disclose only the information required to make these programs work for you and support your membership in them. In addition, we disclose this information to such companies only if you have consented first, including consent implied by your agreement to the membership or participation rules. If you do not want us to disclose that information to the strategic partner, then you must contact the partner directly.   

**Third Party Partners**   
We may enter into agreements and may share your personal information with other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include analyzing data; providing marketing assistance; processing credit card or debit card payments; fulfilling and delivering orders and providing customer service. Additionally, third party providers send promotional e-mails on our behalf to such companies' customers or present advertisements on our behalf, a function called “behavioral targeted advertising.” These providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies (i) to present advertisements tailored to interests you have shown while browsing, (ii) to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before so as to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements, and (iii) to understand the patterns of people who see advertisements. In doing so, the provider collects non-personal data such as your browser type, operating system, websites you have visited, the time of the visits, the content you viewed, ads you viewed, and similar information. The provider may connect information about your visit on our website with information about your visit on other sites and tailor your advertisements based on this combined information. The companies and individuals with which we work have access only to information necessary to perform their functions. They are not allowed to use the information for any other purpose and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the information. We may share non-personal, summary, or aggregate customer data with partners and other third parties. Some third party providers may not be bound by this privacy policy. Their use of third party cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies by these ad network providers may be governed by their own policy. If you wish to not have your personal information used to deliver targeted personalized advertising, you may opt-out of some companies personalized advertising services by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/>. 

**Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.**

**Security**   
When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card or debit card information are encrypted using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. We use SSL technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us and once we have received it. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a restricted-access database that is away from our website database so it is not connected to the Internet, to keep it safe from hackers. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Questions about the security of our website should be directed to [privacy@visiondirect.com](mailto:privacy@visiondirect.com).

**Cookies**   
To personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience, we use a feature of your Internet browser called a cookie. Cookies are small files that your browser places on your computer's hard drive. Although we do not store personal information in cookies, we do tie cookies to a customer member ID which is then used to pull personal information out of the database for identification purposes. Cookies also let us know how you found us (e.g., through a particular website or advertisement). Cookies are not used to access information entered on the secure server. This information can be accessed only when you enter your name and password. If you choose to configure your browser to remove or reject our cookies, you will not be able to make purchases from our websites or take advantage of many of our features, such as Your List™.

**Web Beacons**   
From time to time we contract with third party companies to help us better provide relevant products, services and information to you and to help us effectively measure advertising effectiveness. Some of these companies use cookies and/or web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs). A web beacon is a transparent image that has been placed on a web page and sends a signal when a user has visited that page. A web beacon does not contain any personal information. No information that is personally identifiable to you is transmitted to the third party using the web beacon. The third party is required to protect the privacy of the information it receives using web beacons or cookies and is not allowed to use the information it receives for any purpose beyond what is necessary to assist us. In addition, we may use web beacons in connection with the e-mails we send to our customers, to determine whether and when the images in our e-mail were rendered (which allows us to determine whether the e-mail was opened). This information may then be aggregated and used to assess the effectiveness of our e-mail communications.

**Unsolicited E-mail (SPAM)**   
Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with this privacy policy, we do not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes "harvest" your e-mail address directly from your computer or another person's address book or even obtain your e-mail address through programs that automatically search web pages and e-mail traffic for e-mail addresses. If you opt out of receiving e-mail advertisements from Vision Direct, we may share that information with third parties in order to instruct them not to send advertisements on our behalf to you. If Vision Direct shares opt out information with a third party, we will direct such third party to use this information solely to eliminate potential recipients from any e-mails they send out on our behalf.

Please note that all e-mail that originates from us will either display the drugstore.com™ or Beauty.com™ logo (HTML e-mails) or contain our copyright notice (text e-mails). In addition, our e-mails will contain our corporate address in Bellevue, Washington. If you receive an unsolicited e-mail that you believe is connected with us in any way, please forward the e-mail (as an enclosure) to [abuse@visiondirect.com](mailto:abuse@visiondirect.com) and we will investigate.

**Children**   
We do not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use our website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Linked Websites**   
Our websites may contain links to and from other sites operated and maintained by separate companies. We have no responsibility for linked websites (including the websites of participants in our associate program) and provide these links solely for the convenience of and to provide information to our visitors. The privacy policies of these sites may differ from our policy, so you should always review the privacy statement of each linked website you visit.

**Tell-A-Friend**   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store this information.

**Social Media (Features) and Widgets**   
Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, and the page addresses you visit on our site, and may use a cookie to enable the Features to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**   
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, request deletion, or deactivate it by making the change on the “my account” page or by e-mailing us at [privacy@visiondirect.com](mailto:privacy@visiondirect.com). We will respond to your access request within 30 days.  
As long as your account is active, we will retain your information for the purpose of providing you with our services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at [privacy@visiondirect.com](mailto:privacy@visiondirect.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Your Consent**   
By using our website (including use of our customer service line), you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Unless we clearly state otherwise, the changes to our privacy policy will affect only the information we collect after the effective date of the change.

**Your Comments**   
We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, feel free to drop us an e-mail at [privacy@visiondirect.com](mailto:privacy@visiondirect.com) or write us: 

Vision Direct Inc.  
Privacy Officer  
411 108th Ave NE, Suite 1600  
Bellevue, WA 98004

1-800-847-4663

Last updated: February 07, 2014

Copyright © 2020Vision Direct Inc. All rights reserved.
